

KALLE KEKOMÄKI

Date of Birth: 28/01/1986 Phone: +358443721637 kalle.kekomaki@hotmail.com

Junior Web Designer & Front-end Developer

highly interested in learning more about UI/UX design and programming. I'm versatile, reliable and focused on results with a calm approach to challenges. Having lived and worked in five different countries (Finland, New Zealand, Iceland, Canada and the Czech Republic), I've learned a lot about international projects and best working practices.

COMMUNICATION

Finnish

English

Swedish

SKILLS

Project Management

Customer Service

Content Production & Graphic Design

TECH & SOFTWARE

DESIGN DEVELOPMENT

Photoshop HTML & CSS

InDesign Bootstrap

Figma JavaScript

Adobe Xd ReactJS

Illustrator Node.js & Express

PERSONAL INTERESTS

- Hiking, climbing, mountain biking, ice hockey, padel, squash, travelling
- Graphic design, photography, web design, new technologies

WORK EXPERIENCE

NOVEMBER 2019 - PRESENT

Freelancer & Student, Helsinki / FI

Until June 2020, I was part of a CMS implementation project where I concentrated on creating better online presence for a customer. After that, I've concentrated on finishing my master's degree and studying more about full-stack web development.

JUNE 2019 - NOVEMBER 2019

WheelQ, Helsinki / FI

Project Manager, SaaS Customer Success

- Leading customer onboarding and expansion projects
- Helping B2B customers with technical set-ups and integrations
- Internal process development for SaaS projects

OCTOBER 2015 - DECEMBER 2018

Luxatia International, Prague / CZ

Project Director, Content Production

- In charge of annual events, such as Design Thinking Summit
- Graphic design and content production for event materials
- Market research and sales/marketing campaign planning
- Overall responsibility of B2B events in Europe

JANUARY 2014 - AUGUST 2015

Bluelink International, Prague / CZ CRM Advisor / Air France-KLM Group

- Handling compensation claims and paying out refunds
- Mentoring & training new employees in Mauritius (remotely)
- Daily use of Amadeus and Worldtracer

EDUCATION

AUGUST 2020 - PRESENT

Helsinki Business College

- Full Stack Web Developer Program React & Node
- This is a 17-month full-day intensive education program focusing on HTML, CSS, JavaScript, UI Design & Prototyping, React & Redux, Node & Express, REST API, Unit testing & Quality Assurance, Continuous integrations & AWS

AUGUST 2018 - DECEMBER 2020

LAB University of Applied Sciences

- Master of Business Administration MBA, Digital Solutions
- Studies included e.g. UX/UI design, digital products and services, Data-driven business, Service design

CERTIFICATE COURSES

freeCodeCamp

- Responsive Web Design & Development (300 hours)
- JavaScript Algorithms & Data Structures (300 hours)

Interaction Design Foundation

- Human-Computer Interaction
- User Research Methods and Best Practices
- Psychology of Online Sales
- UX Design & Design Thinking

